Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings and Dom Baron Chant Recordings
Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings
- Toscanini recordings
  - Otello - Dio mi potevi - Verdi, 3/21/1928; hupka_3775; 6824-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Dio mi potevi - Verdi, circa 1919-1923; hupka_3800; CR 2095; 7020-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Dio mi potevi - Verdi, circa 1919-1923; hupka_3803; CM-971; 7020-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Duet, Quando narravi - Verdi (Pt. 1), hupka_3784; CK-1918; 6714-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Duet, Venga la morte - Verdi (Pt. 2), hupka_3787; CK-1919; 6714-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Era la notte - Verdi, 2/13/1907; hupka_1862; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Era la notte - Verdi, circa 1903-1905; hupka_1988; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Esultate - Verdi, 1903; hupka_3933; 10-FT; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Love Duet, Ed io vedea le tue tempie - Verdi (Pt. 2), circa 1919-1923; hupka_3796; CM-1334-2; 7367-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Love Duet, Ed io vedea le tue tempie - Verdi (Pt. 2), circa 1919-1923; hupka_3799; CM-1334-2; 7367-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Love Duet, Gia nella notte denza - Verdi (Pt. 1), circa 1919-1923; hupka_3794; CM-1333-2; 7367-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Love Duet, Gia nella notte denza - Verdi (Pt. 1), circa 1919-1923; hupka_3795; CM-1333-2; 7367-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Mio signore - Verdi, hupka_3788; CR-496-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Morte d'Otello - Verdi, 3/21/1928; hupka_3776; 6824-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Morte d'Otello - Verdi, circa 1919-1923; hupka_3804; CM-972; 7020-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Ninn mi tema - Verdi, hupka_3772; CR-502-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Ninn mi tema - Verdi, 1902; hupka_3935; 269-FT; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Nium mi tema - Verdi, circa 1908-1910; hupka_0871; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Ora e per sempre addio - Verdi, 1903; hupka_3934; 12-FT; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Ora e per sempre addio - Verdi, 10/26/1907; hupka_1150; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Otello's Death - Verdi, 12/12/1944; hupka_3167; Rehearsal; Shellac disc
  - Otello - Otello's Death - Verdi, hupka_3436; CR-2510-3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Questa è una ragna - Verdi, hupka_3770; CR-501-1; Shellac disc
  - Otello - Questa e una ragua - Verdi, circa 1908-1910; hupka_2580; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Salce, salce - Verdi, hupka_0840; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Salce, salce - Verdi, 1/6/1909; hupka_0937; Serial # C 6704; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Si, pel ciel - Verdi, circa 1908-1910; hupka_0869; Serial # 370-A1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Tu! Indietro! - Ora e per sempre - Verdi, hupka_3769; CR-497-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Tu! Indietro! - Ora per sempre addio - Verdi, circa 1919-1923; hupka_3801; CM-977; 7366-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Tu! Indietro! - Ora per sempre addio - Verdi, circa 1919-1923; hupka_3802; CM-977-1; 7366-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Tu?! Indietro! Fuggi! (Ora a per sempre addio) - Verdi, circa 1908-1910; hupka_2568; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Una vela - Esultate - Verdi, circa 1908-1910; hupka_0868; Serial # 360-A1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Una vela - Esultate - Verdi, hupka_3783; CK-1914-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Una vela - Esultate - Verdi, hupka_3792; CM-1321; 7366-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_2755; Side 7; Morning rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_2756; Side 5; Morning rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_2757; Side 6; Morning rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_2758; Side 2; Morning rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_2759; Side 3; Morning rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_2760; Side 4; Morning rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_2761; Side 1; Morning rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_2762; Side 2A; Morning rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_2765; Side 3A; Morning rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_2833; Rehearsal (AM); Sides 1 & 7; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, 11/30/1946; hupka_2834; Rehearsal (AM); Side 6; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Verdi, hupka_3121; Rehearsal; Side 12; Shellac disc
  - Otello - Verdi, hupka_3122; Rehearsal; Side 11; Shellac disc
  - Otello - Verdi, 12/12/1944; hupka_3168; Rehearsal; Side 5; Test; Shellac disc
  - Otello - Vienik l'aula è deserta - Verdi, circa 1908-1910; hupka_0870; Serial # 356-A1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Willow Song (Part 1) - Verdi, 6/8/1926; hupka_0914; Serial # CR 417-1; "Farewell - Covent Garden; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Willow Song (Part 2) - Verdi, 6/8/1926; hupka_0915; Serial # CR 418-1; "Farewell - Covent Garden; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello - Willow Song (Salce, salce) - Verdi, 1/25/1910; hupka_1156; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Otello, Act III - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_0471; Rehearsal; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Otello, Act III & IV - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_0477; Rehearsal; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Otello, Act IV - Verdi, 12/11/1947; hupka_0472; Rehearsal; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Othello (Verdi), 12/11/1947; hupka_0554; Rehearsal; 1/4 inch audio tape
    Otello - Act III (Side 1) & Act IV (Side 2) - Verdi
  - Over There - George M. Cohan [lyricist - Louis Delamarre], [7/11]/1918; hupka_1764; Master # D3-MB-178-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pagliacci - Prolog - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, 1904; hupka_1139; Serial # 227-M; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pagliacci - Prolog - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, 2/27/1907; hupka_1140; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pagliacci - Prologue - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, 10/4/1922; hupka_1051; Shellac disc
  - Pagliacci - Recitar - vesti la guibba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, hupka_1341; Serial # 2SB-2400-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pagliacci - Si Puo? (Prologue) - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, [02/10/1905]; hupka_4064; Serial # 85071; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pagliacci - Vesti la giubba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, Nov. 1902; hupka_1752; "Extremely valuable"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pagliacci - Vesti la giubba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, Nov. 1902; hupka_2034; "Extremely valuable"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pagliacci - Vesti la giubba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, Nov. 1902; hupka_2036; "Extremely valuable"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pagliacci - Vesti la giubba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, Nov. 1902; hupka_2047; Cat # 2875-B; "Extremely valuable; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pagliacci - Vesti la giubba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, 2/1/1904; hupka_2311; 81032; Serial # B-1002; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pagliacci - Vesti la giubba - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, Nov. 1902; hupka_2323; "Extremely valuable"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Panis Angelicus - Franck, hupka_3432; D5-RB-992-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Paride ed Elena - O del mio dolce ardor - Gluck, 1/16/1924; hupka_3465; CK-1428-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Parsifal - Du sieh'st, das ist nicht so - Wagner, [10/19/1903]; hupka_3485; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Parsifal - Good Friday Spell - Wagner, 12/6/1941; hupka_2410; MS 066533-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Parsifal - Good Friday Spell - Wagner (Part 2), 4/9/1944; hupka_3857; Record # D4-RC-178-1A; Shellac disc
  - Parsifal - Good Friday Spell - Wagner (Part 3), 4/9/1944; hupka_3869; Record # D4-RC-179-1A; Shellac disc
  - Parsifal - Good Friday Spell - Wagner (Pt. 1), 4/9/1944; hupka_2027; D4-RC-177-1A; Shellac disc
  - Parsifal - Prelude - Wagner (Part 1), 4/9/1944; hupka_3821; Record # D4-RC-174-1A; Shellac disc
  - Parsifal - Prelude - Wagner (Part 2), 4/9/1944; hupka_3833; Record # D4-RC-175-1A; Shellac disc
  - Parsifal - Prelude - Wagner (Part 3), 4/9/1944; hupka_3845; Record # D4-RC-176-1A; Shellac disc
  - Parsifal - Prelude and Good Friday Spell; Die Walküre - Act I, Scene 3 - Wagner, 4/5/1947; hupka_2794; Studio 8-H; Side 10; Probably a rehearsal - record does not contain all of these pieces, but tracks are taken from the list of the 04/06/47 broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Parsifal - Prelude and Good Friday Spell; Die Walküre - Act I, Scene 3 - Wagner, 4/5/1947; hupka_2795; Studio 8-H; Side 11; Probably a rehearsal - record does not contain all of these pieces, but tracks are taken from the list of the 04/06/47 broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Parsifal - Prelude and Good Friday Spell; Die Walküre - Act I, Scene 3 - Wagner, 4/5/1947; hupka_2883; Studio 8-H; Rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Partita for Violin - Rachmaninoff (Pt. 1), hupka_2152; 072127-2; Shellac disc
  - Partita for Violin - Rachmaninoff (Pt. 1), hupka_2157; 072127-3; Test; Shellac disc
  - Partita for Violin - Rachmaninoff (Pt. 2), hupka_2158; 072128-2; Shellac disc
  - Passacaglia - Bach/Respighi (Part 1), 11/22/1947; hupka_2143; Record # D8-RC-660-1; Shellac disc
  - Passacaglia and Fugue in C minor - Bach/Respighi (Pt. 1), 11/22/1947; hupka_3385; D8-RC-659-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Passacaglia and Fugue in C minor - Bach/Respighi (Pt. 2), 11/22/1947; hupka_3356; D8-RC-660-1; Shellac disc
  - Passacaglia and Fugue in C minor - Bach/Respighi (Pt. 3), 11/22/1947; hupka_3357; D8-RC-661-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Passacaglia in C minor - Bach/Respighi, 11/21-22/1947; hupka_3095; Rehearsal & Broadcast; Side 3; CD on EC; Shellac disc
  - Passacaglia in C minor - Bach/Respighi, 11/21-22/1947; hupka_3096; Rehearsal & Broadcast; Side 2; CD on EC; Shellac disc
  - Passacaglia in C minor - Bach/Respighi, 11/21-22/1947; hupka_3097; Rehearsal & Broadcast; Side 1; CD on EC; Shellac disc
  - Passacaglia in C minor, BWV 582 - Bach/Respighi, hupka_0479; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Passing by - Purcell, hupka_3408; OEA 8824-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pastorale [Symphony No. 6 in F Major (Pastorale), op. 68 - Beethoven?] - Mvt. III, hupka_3631; D5-RC-849-1; Without horn - bars 133-162; Shellac disc
  - Pathétique - ? [Probably Symphony No. 6 in B minor, op. 74 - Tchaikovsky], hupka_0148; The reel most likely contains the Tchaikovsky piece, but it could also be Beethoven's "Piano Sonata No. 8; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Patrie! - Cantabile de Rysoor - Émile Paladihe, [10/11/1920]; hupka_0859; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Paul et Virgine - Chanson du Tigre - Victor Massé, 5/5/1911; hupka_4027; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Paysage Triste - Reynaldo Hahn, hupka_1118; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Pearl Fishers [Les pêcheurs de perles] - Romance - Bizet, 1909; hupka_3915; 1987-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Pearl Fishers [Les pêcheurs de perles] - Romance - Bizet, 1909; hupka_3916; 1987-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Pearl Fishers [Les pêcheurs de perles] - Siccome - Bizet, hupka_0874; IRCC-180-B; 1777-L; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Per la Patria - Bella Italia - Gioacchino Cocchi, hupka_3466; 866-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Per la Patria - Bella Italia - Gioacchino Cocchi, hupka_3469; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Per valli, per boschi - Felice Blangini, 3/27/1907; hupka_0941; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pescatore di Perle - Del tempio al limitan - Bizet, [4/29/1909]; hupka_1182; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Philémon et Baucis - Couplets de Vulcain - Gounod, 1/15/1910; hupka_1248; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Philémon et Baucis - Romance de Sommeil - Gounod, 1/10/1910; hupka_1247; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Phoenetic Punctuation, hupka_3054; Hupka (Imitation), "snoaring"; Repaired crack - but still fragile; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Phoenetic Punctuation, hupka_3056; Shellac disc
  - Piano Concerto - ?, hupka_2135; Shellac disc
  - Piano Concerto No. 1 in B flat minor, op. 23 - Tchaikovsky; Star Spangled Banner - arr. Arturo Toscanini, 4/25/1943; hupka_2063; VinylDisc
  - Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (conc.), hupka_3341; D5-RC-1303-2A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 1), hupka_3338; D5-RC-1300-3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 2), hupka_3339; D5-RC-1301-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 3), hupka_3340; D5-RC-1302-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 1), hupka_3342; D5-RC-1304-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 2), hupka_3343; D5-RC-1305-2A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15 - Mvt. III - Beethoven (conc.), hupka_3345; D5-RC-1307-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15 - Mvt. III - Beethoven (Pt. 1), hupka_3344; D5-RC-1306-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 2 - Mvt. I - Brahms, 5/6/1940; hupka_4161; #MS 050413-1; VinylDisc
  - Piano Concerto No. 2 & Symphony No. 1 - Mvt. I - Brahms, 5/6/1940; hupka_4162; #MS 050416-1; VinylDisc
  - Piano Concerto No. 2 in F minor, op. 21 - Mvt. ? - Chopin (conc.), hupka_1363; D6-RC-5220-1C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 2 in F minor, op. 21 - Mvt. I - Chopin (conc.), hupka_1360; D6-RC-5221-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 2 in F minor, op. 21 - Mvt. I - Chopin (Part 1), hupka_1364; D6-RC-5219-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 2 in F minor, op. 21 - Mvt. II - Chopin (conc.), hupka_1358; D6-RC-5223-1B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 2 in F minor, op. 21 - Mvt. II - Chopin (Part 1), hupka_1359; D6-RC-5222-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 2 in F minor, op. 21 - Mvt. III - Chopin (conc.), hupka_1356; D6-RC-5225-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 2 in F minor, op. 21 - Mvt. III - Chopin (Part 1), hupka_1357; D6-RC-5224-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 3 in c minor, op. 37 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 10/29/1944; hupka_3606; D5-RC-37-1B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 3 in c minor, op. 37 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 10/29/1944; hupka_3607; D5-RC-38-1B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 3 in c minor, op. 37 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 10/29/1944; hupka_3608; D5-RC-39-1B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 3 in c minor, op. 37 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 4), 10/29/1944; hupka_3609; D5-RC-40-1C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 3 in c minor, op. 37 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 10/29/1944; hupka_3610; D5-RC-41-1B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 3 in c minor, op. 37 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 10/29/1944; hupka_3611; D5-RC-42-1B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 3 in c minor, op. 37 - Mvt. III - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 10/29/1944; hupka_3612; D5-RC-43-2B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 3 in c minor, op. 37 - Mvt. III - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 10/29/1944; hupka_3615; D5-RC-44-1D; lacquer; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Concerto No. 4 in G Major, op. 58 - Beethoven, 2/23/1936; hupka_0249; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Piano Concerto No. 27, K. 595 - Mozart, 2/23/1936; hupka_0250; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Piano Sonata No. 14 in C sharp minor (Moonlight), op. 27, No. 2 - Beethoven, hupka_3644; D6-RC-6419-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Sonata No. 14 in C sharp minor (Moonlight), op. 27, No. 2 - Beethoven, hupka_3645; D6-RC-6420-1C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Sonata No. 14 in C sharp minor (Moonlight), op. 27, No. 2 - Beethoven, hupka_3646; D6-RC-6421-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Sonata No. 15 in D Major, op. 28 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven, hupka_2165; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Sonata No. 21 - Mvt. III - Beethoven (Part 1), hupka_1284; D4-RC-693-1A; "Ordered 'destroy' by Horowitz; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Sonata No. 21 in C Major (Waldstein), op. 53 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 1), hupka_3647; D4-RC-690-1; Ordered destroy - by Horowitz; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Sonata No. 21 in C Major (Waldstein), op. 53 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 2), hupka_3648; D4-RC-691-1A; Ordered destroy - by Horowitz; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Sonata No. 21 in C Major (Waldstein), op. 53 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 1), hupka_3649; D4-RC-692-1A; Ordered destroy - by Horowitz; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Piano Sonata No. 21 in C Major (Waldstein), op. 53 - Mvt. III - Beethoven (conc.), hupka_3643; D4-RC-694-1A; Ordered destroy - by Horowitz; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pick the Winner (A Race Horse Game for Parties), 24022-A, hupka_0814; Shellac disc
  - Pictures at an Exhibition - Mussorgsky (arr. Ravel) - Pt. 1 & 3, 2/19/1945; hupka_2680; Benefit concert - Not Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pictures at an Exhibition - Mussorgsky (arr. Ravel) - Pt. 2; La Valse - Ravel, 2/19/1945; hupka_2679; Benefit concert - Not Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pictures at an Exhibition - The Hut of Baba Yaga, The Great Gate of Kiev - Mussorgsky (arr. Ravel), 2/14/1948; hupka_2194; Broadcast - Studio 8-H; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pictures from an Exhibition - Mussorgsky (Part 1), hupka_1293; D7-RC-7968-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pictures from an Exhibition - Mussorgsky (Part 2), hupka_1292; D7-RC-7969-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pictures from an Exhibition - Mussorgsky (Part 3), hupka_1291; D7-RC-7970-4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pictures from an Exhibition - Mussorgsky (Part 4), hupka_1285; Serial # D7-RC-7972-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pictures from an Exhibition - Mussorgsky (Part 4), hupka_1286; Serial # D7-RC-7971-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pictures from an Exhibition - Mussorgsky (Part 6), hupka_1303; D7-RC-7974-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pines of Rome - Respighi; La Mer - Debussy, hupka_0052; Test tape; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Pines of Rome - Respighi; La Mer - Debussy, hupka_0054; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Plaisir d'amour - Johann P.A. Martini, [4/1/1907]; hupka_1181; Shellac disc
  - Polonaise [op. ?] - Chopin, 2/28/1952; hupka_2166; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pre-concert announcement; orchestra warm-up; Parsifal and Die Walküre excerpts, 12/12/1944; hupka_3170; Shellac disc
  - Prelude to the Afternoon of a Faun - Debussy (Part 1), 2/11/1945; hupka_2617; Record # D5-RC-103-1; Shellac disc
  - Prelude to the Afternoon of a Faun - Debussy (Part 2), 2/11/1945; hupka_2629; Record # D5-RC-104-1; Shellac disc
  - Prelude to the Afternoon of a Faun, L. 86 - Debussy; Fountains of Fome - Respighi, 2/17/1951; hupka_4127; Parts 1 & 2; E1-LCC-3651 & 3652; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Priere - Benjamin Godard, [1/24/1917]; hupka_3688; B-19126; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Prince Igor - Daylight Slowly Fades - Alexander Borodin, 7/23/1921; hupka_3906; CC 3212-2; Shellac disc
  - Prince Igor - Daylight Slowly Fades - Alexander Borodin, 7/23/1921; hupka_3909; CC 3212-2; Shellac disc
  - Prince Igor - Daylight Slowly Fades - Alexander Borodin, 7/23/1921; hupka_3910; CC 3212-2; Shellac disc
  - Prince Igor - Song of Prince Galitsky - Aleksandr Borodin, [03/16/1927]; hupka_4090; 1237-A; BE 26100; Shellac disc
  - Profete [Le Prophète] - Re del cielo dei beati (Triumphal Hymn) - Giacomo Meyerbeer, circa 1908-1910; hupka_2592; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 2: ?, hupka_2722; Record # ND3-MM-5506; Part 2 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 2: ?, hupka_2723; Record # ND3-MM-5508; Part 4 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 2: Indrodução da ópera Khovanstchina [Khovanshchina - Introduction] - Mussorgsky; A Tempestade [The Tempest] - Tchaikovsky; Sinfonia Primeira [Symphony No. 1] - Part 1 - Shostakovich, hupka_2721; Record # ND3-MM-5507 & 5505; Parts 1 & 3 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 3: Abertura da ópera Oberon [Oberon - Opening] - Weber; Sinfonia No. 92, em Sol maior [Symphony No. 92 in G Major] - Haydn; Os Pinheiros de Roma [The Pines of Rome] - Respighi, hupka_2724; Record # ND3-MM-5553 & 5555; Parts 1 & 3 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 3: Sinfonia No. 92, em Sol maior [Symphony No. 92 in G Major] - Haydn; Os Pinheiros de Roma [The Pines of Rome] - Respighi, hupka_2731; Record # ND3-MM-5554 & 5556; Parts 2 & 4 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 4: Sinfonia No. 2 em Si bemol [Symphony No. 2 in B flat Major] - Schubert; O Moldau - Smetana, hupka_2733; Record # ND3-MM-5558 & 5560; Parts 2 & 4 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 4: Taming of the Shrew - Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco; Sinfonia No. 2 em Si bemol [Symphony No. 2 in B flat Major] - Schubert; Scherzo Rainha Mab [Roméo et Juliette - Queen Mab Scherzo] - Berlioz, hupka_2732; Record # ND3-MM-5557 & 5559; Parts 1 & 3 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 5: La Boheme - Act III & IV - Puccini, hupka_2913; Parts 5 & 7 of 8; Master No. 17-3347A & 17-3306; Record # ND6-MM-4147-2 & ND6-MM-4149; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 5: La Boheme - Puccini, hupka_2291; Parts 1 & 3 of 8; Master No. 17-3301 & 17-3292; Record # ND6-MM-4143 & ND6-MM-4145; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 5: La Boheme - Puccini, hupka_2292; Parts 2 & 4 of 8; Master No. 17-3302 & 17-3303; Record # ND6-MM-4144 & ND6-MM-4146; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 5: La Boheme - Puccini, hupka_2293; Parts 6 & 8 of 8; Master No. 17-3305 & 17-3307; Record # ND6-MM-4148 & ND6-MM-4150; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 5: La Boheme - Puccini, hupka_2294; Parts 5 & 7 of 8; Master No. 17-3347A & 17-3306; Record # ND6-MM-4147-2 & ND6-MM-4149; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 5: Quatro Igrejas Brasileiras [Fantasias brasileiras, No. 1- 4] - Francisco Mignone; Concêrto para Piano e Orquestra em F Maior [Piano Concerto in F] - Gershwin, hupka_2729; Record # ND3-MM-5517 & 5519; Parts 1 & 3 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 5: Quatro Igrejas Brasileiras [Fantasias brasileiras, No. 1- 4] - Francisco Mignone; Concêrto para Piano e Orquestra em F Maior [Piano Concerto in F] - Gershwin, hupka_2730; Record # ND3-MM-5518 & 5520; Parts 2 & 4 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 6: I Lombardi alla prima crocciata; Otello - Dances; Himno de las Naciones [Inno delle Nazioni] - Verdi, hupka_2687; Record # ND3-MM-3244 & 3246; Parts 2 & 4 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 6: La Fuerza del Sino [La Forza del destino] - Overture; Nabucco - Coro [probably Chorus of the Hebrew Slaves]; La Traviata - Prelude to Act III - Verdi, hupka_2686; Record # ND3-MM-3243 & 3245; Parts 1 & 3 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 6: Prelúdio e Encanto da Sexta-Feira Santa [Parsifal - Good Friday Spell] - Wagner; Concêrto para Violino e Orquestra en Mi Menor [Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64] - Mendelssohn, hupka_2734; Record # ND3-MM-5521 & 5523; Parts 1 & 3 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 6: Prelúdio e Encanto da Sexta-Feira Santa [Parsifal - Good Friday Spell] - Wagner; Concêrto para Violino e Orquestra en Mi Menor [Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64] - Mendelssohn, hupka_2735; Record # ND3-MM-5522 & 5524; Parts 2 & 4 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 10: ?, hupka_2694; Record # ND3-MM-3366; Part 1 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 10: ?, hupka_2696; Record # ND3-MM-3368; Part 3 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 10: Sinfonía No. 1 en do mayor [Symphony No. 1 in C Major, op. 21] - Beethoven; La Mar [La Mer] - Debussy, hupka_2695; Record # ND3-MM-3367 & 3369; Parts 2 & 4 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 13: ?, hupka_2697; Record # ND3-MM-3298; Part 1 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 13: ?, hupka_2699; Record # ND3-MM-3352; Part 3 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Program No. 13: Abertura e Adagio de As Crianças de Prometeu [The Creatures of Prometheus - Adagio & Allegretto]; Sinfonia No. 6 [Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68] - Beethoven, hupka_2736; Record # ND3-MM-5549 & 5551 Parts 1 & 3 of 4; Lacquer discs/acetates